kjrocker.com 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy

## Who we are

Blog www.kjrocker.com , Is maintained by Kj Rocker F.Z.E Kj Rocker F.Z.E, A digital Marketing Company Based in UAE. Our Official Address Is SM-Office – H1-115B Ajman Free Zone authority , Ajman,UAE

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and make use of personal information. The following outlines our Privacy Policy.

When accessing our Website, Kj Rocker F.Z.E will learn certain information about you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies?”) and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site, your IP address.

 **What Are Cookies?**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

 **IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

 **Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone.

 **How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer service and making available other items and services to our customers and prospective customers.

Kj Rocker F.Z.E will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection.

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.

 **  
A Special Note About Children**

Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask that minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

 **How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email.

Kj Rocker F.Z.E may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, Kj Rocker F.Z.E uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

 **Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

## Rights to Your Information According to GDPR

GDPR stands for the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679, which is a European Union law governing privacy and data protection for all residents of the EU. The provisions of GDPR can be also applied to how data is processed and verified (more on that later) outside the European Union.

Generally speaking, the GDPR represents a new set of rules intended to empower the citizens of the European Union to control their personal information. In accordance with the applicable laws, users are authorized to access and modify their own data held by the companies, which includes data collection, ad tracking, surveys, cookies, location data, and every other bit of a user’s “digital footprint”. Users are also entitled to transmit their personal details to other organizations. The GDPR also enforces companies to determine their in-house data security policies.

At any time through the web interface provided as part of the Services or via [contact us](https://www.kjrocker.com/contact/) page you have the right:

  * to access your personal information that we hold;
  * to request the rectification of your personal information that we hold;
  * to request the erasure of your personal information that we hold;
  * to request to restrict processing of your personal information;
  * to object to processing of your personal information by us;
  * to request to transfer your personal information that we hold (e.g. data portability);
  * to file a complaint to a supervisory authority in your jurisdiction; and
  * to withdraw any consent related to your personal information given by you.

We will process your requests to us within 30 days. We will also notify you within and a relevant supervisory authority within 72 hours from a breach related to your personal information that we hold.

We have assigned a Data Protection Officer (DPO) who may be reached via dpo@kjrocker.com. Our DPO is tasked with ensuring that we acknowledge and abide by our data protection responsibilities.

We will not store personal information for more than 6 months from the date of your last active session on the Site or for more than 6 months from the date of termination of an agreement between Kjrocker and you (whichever is earlier).

 **Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with our web site, please contact us.

Kj Rocker F.Z.E  
SM-Office – H1-115B Ajman Free Zone authority , Ajman,UAE  
042 737274  
contact@kjrocker.com
